<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<propiedades>
  <propiedad>
    <id>22447562</id>
    <numagencia>11855</numagencia>
    <calidades/>
    <provincia>BALEARES</provincia>
    <key_loca>100899</key_loca>
    <key_tipo>499</key_tipo>
    <tipovpo>0</tipovpo>
    <vpo_name> </vpo_name>
    <destacado>1</destacado>
    <antiguedad>2026</antiguedad>
    <tipo_ofer>Chalet</tipo_ofer>
    <fecha>2024-09-05 19:02:02</fecha>
    <fechaact>2025-07-21 12:34:26</fechaact>
    <keypromo>22587405</keypromo>
    <opcioncompra>0</opcioncompra>
    <aconsultar>0</aconsultar>
    <latitud>39.5209579</latitud>
    <altitud>3.3076535</altitud>
    <aseos>0</aseos>
    <banyos>2</banyos>
    <carpint>Lacado Blanco</carpint>
    <carpext>Climalit</carpext>
    <comunidadincluida>0</comunidadincluida>
    <tfachada/>
    <tcocina/>
    <tpostigo/>
    <tbano/>
    <tinterior><![CDATA[]]></tinterior>
    <distmar>0</distmar>
    <planta>0</planta>
    <conservacion>Obra Nueva</conservacion>
    <gastos_com>0</gastos_com>
    <habdobles>2</habdobles>
    <habitaciones>0</habitaciones>
    <m_cons>120.00</m_cons>
    <m_parcela>293</m_parcela>
    <m_uties>75.00</m_uties>
    <m_cocina>0.00</m_cocina>
    <m_comedor>0.00</m_comedor>
    <m_terraza>0.00</m_terraza>
    <numplanta>2</numplanta>
    <orientacion/>
    <salon>1</salon>
    <precioinmo>388000</precioinmo>
    <preciotraspaso>0</preciotraspaso>
    <precioalq>0</precioalq>
    <outlet>0</outlet>
    <ref>RA464</ref>
    <accion>Vender</accion>
    <ciudad>Manacor</ciudad>
    <cp>07680</cp>
    <zona>Cala mandia</zona>
    <adaptadominus>0</adaptadominus>
    <airecentral>0</airecentral>
    <aire_con>1</aire_con>
    <alarma>0</alarma>
    <alarmaincendio>0</alarmaincendio>
    <alarmarobo>0</alarmarobo>
    <arma_empo>1</arma_empo>
    <ascensor>0</ascensor>
    <balcon>1</balcon>
    <bar>0</bar>
    <jardin>1</jardin>
    <barbacoa>0</barbacoa>
    <cajafuerte>0</cajafuerte>
    <keycalefa>0</keycalefa>
    <keysuelo>0</keysuelo>
    <calefacentral>0</calefacentral>
    <calefaccion>0</calefaccion>
    <chimenea>0</chimenea>
    <depoagua>0</depoagua>
    <descalcificador>0</descalcificador>
    <despensa>0</despensa>
    <diafano>0</diafano>
    <electro>1</electro>
    <esquina>0</esquina>
    <galeria>0</galeria>
    <plaza_gara>2</plaza_gara>
    <garajedoble>0</garajedoble>
    <gasciudad>0</gasciudad>
    <gimnasio>1</gimnasio>
    <habjuegos>0</habjuegos>
    <tipomensual>MES</tipomensual>
    <hidromasaje>0</hidromasaje>
    <jacuzzi>0</jacuzzi>
    <lavanderia>1</lavanderia>
    <linea_tlf>0</linea_tlf>
    <luminoso>0</luminoso>
    <ibi>0.00</ibi>
    <luz>1</luz>
    <muebles>0</muebles>
    <ojobuey>0</ojobuey>
    <parking>2</parking>
    <patio>0</patio>
    <piscina_com>1</piscina_com>
    <piscina_prop>0</piscina_prop>
    <preinstaacc>0</preinstaacc>
    <primera_line>0</primera_line>
    <puerta_blin>1</puerta_blin>
    <satelite>0</satelite>
    <sauna>0</sauna>
    <solarium>0</solarium>
    <sotano>0</sotano>
    <mirador>0</mirador>
    <apartseparado>0</apartseparado>
    <bombafriocalor>1</bombafriocalor>
    <buhardilla>0</buhardilla>
    <pergola>0</pergola>
    <tv>1</tv>
    <terraza>1</terraza>
    <terrazaacris>0</terrazaacris>
    <todoext>2</todoext>
    <trastero>0</trastero>
    <urbanizacion>1</urbanizacion>
    <nplazasparking>1</nplazasparking>
    <vestuarios>0</vestuarios>
    <vistasalmar>0</vistasalmar>
    <energialetra>D</energialetra>
    <energiarecibido>1</energiarecibido>
    <energiavalor>0</energiavalor>
    <emisionesletra>A</emisionesletra>
    <emisionesvalor>0</emisionesvalor>
    <cocina_inde>3</cocina_inde>
    <keyelectricidad>2</keyelectricidad>
    <keyfachada>21</keyfachada>
    <keyagua>3</keyagua>
    <keyvista>0</keyvista>
    <keytecho>0</keytecho>
    <montana>0</montana>
    <rural>0</rural>
    <costa>1</costa>
    <vallado>0</vallado>
    <autobuses>0</autobuses>
    <centros_comerciales>0</centros_comerciales>
    <tranvia>0</tranvia>
    <zonas_infantiles>0</zonas_infantiles>
    <colegios>0</colegios>
    <arboles>0</arboles>
    <hospitales>0</hospitales>
    <tren>0</tren>
    <metro>0</metro>
    <golf>1</golf>
    <descrip1><![CDATA[VISITAS AL PISO PILOTO DISPONIBLES.~Presentamos Sunrise Bay Residences, un complejo residencial exclusivo en la costa Este de Mallorca, un enclave único y natural en la isla más paradisíaca del Mediterráneo.~Disfruta de sus piscinas exteriores en diferentes parcelas del complejo, gimnasio dotado de equipamiento deportivo, sala de cinema, gastrobar, business center, zona de relax equipada con sauna, chorros de agua e hidromasaje.~~En Sunrise Bay Residences encontrarás villas de 2, 3 y 4 dormitorios de diferentes tipologías de hasta 150 m² para que elijas aquella que mejor se adapta a tu estilo de vida y disfrutes al aire libre del máximo bienestar. Infórmate sin compromiso y te facilitaremos toda la información que necesites.~~Cada villa se ha diseñado cuidadosamente consiguiendo que se integre perfectamente con el ambiente mediterráneo de la zona. La distribución estratégica permite la conexión interior y exterior en la mayoría de estancias para recibir la máxima entrada de luz natural, dando como resultado estancias amplias, luminosas y acogedoras.~~Sus amplios ventanales unen terrazas y salones para maximizar el espacio y lograr que la luz de Mallorca llegue a cada rincón, gracias también a una distribución abierta y fluida.~~Están dotadas de todo lo necesario para una vida cómoda. ~Carpintería exterior de PVC o aluminio lacado con rotura de puente térmico y doble acristalamiento con cámara de aire, para una mayor eficiencia energética garantizando el confort térmico en la vivienda, puerta de acceso a la vivienda de seguridad, puertas interiores de paso lacado en blanco, armarios empotrados, tarima flotante laminada de acabado sintético, baños equipados con sanitarios, plato de ducha y griferías con suelo de porcelánico, cocinas con muebles altos y bajos con opciones de almacenamiento, encimera de tonalidad a juego con las puertas del mobiliario, electrodomésticos.~Su instalación de frío / calor otorga un extra de bienestar y comodidad.~~Todas las villas se distribuyen en dos plantas y cuentan con área de terraza en planta inferior y planta superior, plaza de garaje exterior y posible instalación de pérgola, aprovechando al máximo el entorno y el clima de la isla. Se ofrece, además, una opción de upgrade para los propietarios que quieran añadir una piscina privada.~~Situado en Cala Romántica, a solo cinco minutos de la cala Estany d'en Mas, Sunrise Bay Residences es un verdadero oasis de paz en una zona exclusiva de Mallorca. ~Un lugar para disfrutar de la esencia mediterránea y establecer su nuevo hogar.~~Ven a visitarlo y descúbrelo en primera persona.~~SIGUENOS EN REDES: ~FACEBOOK RBconforthouse.~INSTAGRAM RBconforthouse.~]]></descrip1>
    <titulo1><![CDATA[Promoción Sunrise Bay Mallorca]]></titulo1>
    <titulo2><![CDATA[Sunrise Bay Mallorca Promotion]]></titulo2>
    <descrip2><![CDATA[SHOW APARTMENT VISITS AVAILABLE.~Introducing Sunrise Bay Residences, an exclusive residential complex on the east coast of Mallorca, a unique and natural enclave on the most paradisiacal island in the Mediterranean.~Enjoy its outdoor swimming pools on different plots of the complex, a gym equipped with sports equipment, a cinema room, a gastrobar, a business centre, a relaxation area equipped with a sauna, water jets and a hydromassage.~~At Sunrise Bay Residences you will find 2, 3 and 4 bedroom villas of different types of up to 150 m² so that you can choose the one that best suits your lifestyle and enjoy the maximum well-being outdoors. Find out without obligation and we will provide you with all the information you need.~~Each villa has been carefully designed to blend perfectly with the Mediterranean atmosphere of the area. The strategic distribution allows for the interior and exterior connection in most rooms to receive the maximum amount of natural light, resulting in spacious, bright and welcoming rooms.~~Its large windows connect terraces and living rooms to maximize space and ensure that the light of Mallorca reaches every corner, thanks also to an open and fluid layout.~~They are equipped with everything necessary for a comfortable life.~Exterior carpentry made of PVC or lacquered aluminum with thermal break and double glazing with an air chamber, for greater energy efficiency guaranteeing thermal comfort in the home, security access door to the home, white lacquered interior doors, built-in wardrobes, synthetic laminated floating flooring, bathrooms equipped with toilets, shower tray and taps with porcelain flooring, kitchens with upper and upper cabinets with storage options, countertop in a color matching the doors of the furniture, appliances.~Its hot/cold installation provides extra well-being and comfort.~~All villas are distributed over two floors and have a terrace area on the lower and upper floors, an outdoor parking space and possible installation of a pergola, making the most of the environment and climate of the island. An upgrade option is also available for owners who want to add a private pool.~~Located in Cala Romántica, just five minutes from Estany d'en Mas cove, Sunrise Bay Residences is a true oasis of peace in an exclusive area of ​​Mallorca.~A place to enjoy the Mediterranean essence and establish your new home.~~Come visit it and discover it first hand.~~FOLLOW US ON SOCIAL MEDIA:~FACEBOOK RBconforthouse.~INSTAGRAM RBconforthouse.~]]></descrip2>
    <titulo3><![CDATA[]]></titulo3>
    <descrip3><![CDATA[BESUCHE DER MUSTERWOHNUNG VERFÜGBAR.Wir präsentieren Sunrise Bay Residences, eine exklusive Wohnanlage an der Ostküste Mallorcas, eine einzigartige und natürliche Enklave auf der paradiesischsten Insel des Mittelmeers.Genießen Sie die Außenpools auf verschiedenen Grundstücken des Komplexes, ein mit Sportgeräten ausgestattetes Fitnessstudio, ein Kino, eine Gastrobar, ein Business Center und einen Ruhebereich mit Sauna, Wasserstrahlen und Hydromassage.In Sunrise Bay Residences finden Sie Villen mit 2, 3 und 4 Schlafzimmern in verschiedenen Typologien von bis zu 150 m², damit Sie diejenige auswählen können, die am besten zu Ihrem Lebensstil passt und das maximale Wohlbefinden im Freien genießen können. Informieren Sie sich unverbindlich und wir stellen Ihnen alle Informationen zur Verfügung, die Sie benötigen.Jede Villa wurde sorgfältig entworfen, um sich perfekt in das mediterrane Ambiente der Gegend einzufügen. Die strategische Aufteilung ermöglicht die Verbindung von Innen und Außen in den meisten Räumen, um maximalen Lichteinfall zu erhalten, was zu geräumigen, hellen und einladenden Räumen führt.Die großen Fenster verbinden Terrassen und Wohnzimmer, um den Raum zu maximieren und das Licht Mallorcas in jeden Winkel zu bringen, auch dank einer offenen und fließenden Aufteilung.Sie sind mit allem ausgestattet, was für ein komfortables Leben benötigt wird.Außenschreinereiarbeiten aus PVC oder lackiertem Aluminium mit thermischer Trennung und Doppelverglasung mit Luftkammer für eine höhere Energieeffizienz, die den thermischen Komfort im Haus garantiert, Sicherheitseingangstür, weiß lackierte Innentüren, Einbauschränke, Laminatparkett mit synthetischer Oberfläche, Badezimmer ausgestattet mit Sanitäranlagen, Duschwanne und Armaturen mit Porzellanboden, Küchen mit Ober- und Unterschränken mit Stauraummöglichkeiten, Arbeitsplatte im Farbton passend zu den Möbeltüren, Elektrogeräte.Ihre Kälte-/Wärmeinstallation sorgt für ein Plus an Wohlbefinden und Komfort.Alle Villen verteilen sich auf zwei Etagen und verfügen über eine Terrasse im Erdgeschoss und im Obergeschoss, einen Außenstellplatz und die Möglichkeit, eine Pergola zu installieren, um die Umgebung und das Klima der Insel optimal zu nutzen. Darüber hinaus wird den Eigentümern, die einen privaten Pool hinzufügen möchten, eine Upgrade-Option angeboten.Sunrise Bay Residences liegt in Cala Romántica, nur fünf Minuten von der Bucht Estany d'en Mas entfernt, und ist eine wahre Oase der Ruhe in einer exklusiven Gegend Mallorcas.Ein Ort, um die mediterrane Essenz zu genießen und Ihr neues Zuhause zu gründen.Kommen Sie und besuchen Sie es und entdecken Sie es persönlich.BESUCHEN SIE UNSERE WEBSITE: rbconforthouse. com, um alle Wohnungen kennenzulernen, die wir derzeit sowohl zur Miete als auch zum Verkauf anbieten. FOLGEN SIE UNS IN DEN NETZWERKEN:FACEBOOK RBconforthouse.INSTAGRAM RBconforthouse.~]]></descrip3>
    <titulo4><![CDATA[]]></titulo4>
    <descrip4><![CDATA[VISITES DE L'APPARTEMENT TÉMOIN DISPONIBLES.Nous vous présentons Sunrise Bay Residences, un complexe résidentiel exclusif sur la côte est de Majorque, une enclave unique et naturelle sur l'île la plus paradisiaque de la Méditerranée.Profitez de ses piscines extérieures dans différentes parcelles du complexe, d'une salle de sport équipée d'équipements sportifs, d'une salle de cinéma, d'un gastrobar, d'un centre d'affaires, d'un espace détente équipé d'un sauna, de jets d'eau et d'un bain à remous.Dans Sunrise Bay Residences, vous trouverez des villas de 2, 3 et 4 chambres de différentes typologies jusqu'à 150 m² pour que vous choisissiez celle qui s'adapte le mieux à votre style de vie et profitiez au maximum du bien-être en plein air. Renseignez-vous sans engagement et nous vous fournirons toutes les informations dont vous avez besoin.Chaque villa a été soigneusement conçue pour s'intégrer parfaitement à l'environnement méditerranéen de la région. La distribution stratégique permet la connexion intérieure et extérieure dans la plupart des pièces pour recevoir le maximum de lumière naturelle, ce qui donne des pièces spacieuses, lumineuses et accueillantes.Ses grandes fenêtres relient les terrasses et les salons pour maximiser l'espace et faire en sorte que la lumière de Majorque atteigne chaque recoin, grâce également à une distribution ouverte et fluide.Elles sont dotées de tout le nécessaire pour une vie confortable.Menuiserie extérieure en PVC ou aluminium laqué avec rupture de pont thermique et double vitrage avec chambre à air, pour une plus grande efficacité énergétique garantissant le confort thermique dans le logement, porte d'accès au logement de sécurité, portes intérieures de passage laquées en blanc, placards, sol stratifié flottant de finition synthétique, salles de bains équipées de sanitaires, receveur de douche et robinetterie avec sol en grès cérame, cuisines avec meubles hauts et bas avec options de rangement, plan de travail de la même teinte que les portes du mobilier, électroménagers.Son installation de froid/chaleur offre un supplément de bien-être et de confort.Toutes les villas sont réparties sur deux étages et disposent d'une terrasse à l'étage inférieur et à l'étage supérieur, d'une place de parking extérieure et d'une possibilité d'installation de pergola, profitant au maximum de l'environnement et du climat de l'île. Une option de surclassement est également proposée aux propriétaires qui souhaitent ajouter une piscine privée.Situé à Cala Romántica, à seulement cinq minutes de la crique Estany d'en Mas, Sunrise Bay Residences est une véritable oasis de paix dans une zone exclusive de Majorque.Un lieu pour profiter de l'essence méditerranéenne et établir votre nouveau foyer.Venez le visiter et découvrez-le en personne.VISITEZ NOTRE SITE WEB: rbconforthouse. com pour connaître tous les logements dont nous disposons actuellement à la location ou à la vente. SUIVEZ-NOUS SUR LES RÉSEAUX:FACEBOOK RBconforthouse.INSTAGRAM RBconforthouse.~]]></descrip4>
    <titulo5><![CDATA[]]></titulo5>
    <descrip5><![CDATA[BEZOEKEN VAN HET MODELAPPARTEMENT BESCHIKBAAR.We presenteren Sunrise Bay Residences, een exclusief wooncomplex aan de oostkust van Mallorca, een unieke en natuurlijke enclave op het meest paradijselijke eiland van de Middellandse Zee.Geniet van de buitenzwembaden op verschillende percelen van het complex, een fitnessruimte met sporttoestellen, een bioscoopzaal, een gastrobar, een business center en een ontspanningsruimte met sauna, waterstralen en hydromassage.In Sunrise Bay Residences vindt u villa's met 2, 3 en 4 slaapkamers van verschillende typologieën tot 150 m² zodat u degene kunt kiezen die het beste bij uw levensstijl past en kunt genieten van het maximale welzijn in de buitenlucht. Informeer uzelf vrijblijvend en wij verstrekken u alle informatie die u nodig heeft.Elke villa is zorgvuldig ontworpen zodat deze perfect integreert met de mediterrane sfeer van het gebied. De strategische indeling maakt de verbinding tussen binnen en buiten in de meeste kamers mogelijk om de maximale hoeveelheid natuurlijk licht binnen te laten, wat resulteert in ruime, lichte en gezellige kamers.De grote ramen verbinden terrassen en woonkamers om de ruimte te maximaliseren en ervoor te zorgen dat het licht van Mallorca elke hoek bereikt, dankzij een open en vloeiende indeling.Ze zijn uitgerust met alles wat nodig is voor een comfortabel leven.Buitenschrijnwerk van PVC of gelakt aluminium met thermische onderbreking en dubbele beglazing met spouw, voor een grotere energie-efficiëntie die het thermische comfort in de woning garandeert, veiligheidsdeur voor toegang tot de woning, witte gelakte binnendeuren, inbouwkasten, synthetisch afgewerkte laminaatparketvloer, badkamers uitgerust met sanitair, douchebak en kranen met porseleinen vloer, keukens met boven- en onderkasten met opbergmogelijkheden, werkblad in bijpassende kleur met de meubeldeuren, huishoudelijke apparaten.De installatie van koude / warmte zorgt voor extra welzijn en comfort.Alle villa's zijn verdeeld over twee verdiepingen en hebben een terras op de begane grond en de bovenverdieping, een parkeerplaats buiten en de mogelijkheid om een pergola te installeren, om optimaal te profiteren van de omgeving en het klimaat van het eiland. Er wordt ook een upgrade-optie aangeboden voor eigenaren die een privézwembad willen toevoegen.Sunrise Bay Residences ligt in Cala Romántica, op slechts vijf minuten van de baai Estany d'en Mas, en is een ware oase van rust in een exclusieve zone van Mallorca.Een plek om te genieten van de mediterrane essentie en uw nieuwe thuis te vestigen.Kom het bezoeken en ontdek het zelf.BEZOEK ONZE WEBSITE: rbconforthouse. com om alle woningen te zien die we momenteel zowel te huur als te koop hebben. VOLG ONS OP SOCIALE MEDIA:FACEBOOK RBconforthouse.INSTAGRAM RBconforthouse.~]]></descrip5>
    <titulo6><![CDATA[]]></titulo6>
    <descrip6><![CDATA[]]></descrip6>
    <titulo7><![CDATA[]]></titulo7>
    <descrip7><![CDATA[]]></descrip7>
    <titulo8><![CDATA[]]></titulo8>
    <descrip8><![CDATA[]]></descrip8>
    <titulo9><![CDATA[]]></titulo9>
    <descrip9><![CDATA[]]></descrip9>
    <titulo10><![CDATA[]]></titulo10>
    <descrip10><![CDATA[]]></descrip10>
    <titulo11><![CDATA[]]></titulo11>
    <descrip11><![CDATA[]]></descrip11>
    <titulo12><![CDATA[]]></titulo12>
    <descrip12><![CDATA[VISITES AL PIS PILOT DISPONIBLES.Us presentem Sunrise Bay Residences, un complex residencial exclusiu a la costa est de Mallorca, un enclavament únic i natural a l'illa més paradisíaca del Mediterrani.Gaudeix de les seves piscines exteriors en diferents parcel·les del complex, gimnàs dotat d'equipament esportiu, sala de cinema, gastrobar, business center, zona de relax equipada amb sauna, dolls d'aigua i hidromassatge.A Sunrise Bay Residences trobaràs viles de 2, 3 i 4 dormitoris de diferents tipologies de fins a 150 m² perquè escullis aquella que millor s'adapta al teu estil de vida i gaudeixis a l'aire lliure del màxim benestar. Informa't sense compromís i et facilitarem tota la informació que necessitis.Cada vila s'ha dissenyat acuradament aconseguint que s'integri perfectament amb l'ambient mediterrani de la zona. La distribució estratègica permet la connexió interior i exterior en la majoria d'estades per rebre la màxima entrada de llum natural, donant com a resultat estades àmplies, lluminoses i acollidores.Els seus amplis finestrals uneixen terrasses i salons per maximitzar l'espai i aconseguir que la llum de Mallorca arribi a cada racó, gràcies també a una distribució oberta i fluida.Estan dotades de tot el necessari per a una vida còmoda.Fusteria exterior de PVC o alumini lacat amb trencament de pont tèrmic i doble vidre amb cambra d'aire, per a una major eficiència energètica garantint el confort tèrmic a l'habitatge, porta d'accés a l'habitatge de seguretat, portes interiors de pas lacades en blanc, armaris encastats, tarima flotant laminada d'acabat sintètic, banys equipats amb sanitaris, plat de dutxa i aixetes amb terra de porcellànic, cuines amb mobles alts i baixos amb opcions d'emmagatzematge, taulell de tonalitat a joc amb les portes del mobiliari, electrodomèstics.La seva instal·lació de fred / calor atorga un extra de benestar i comoditat.Totes les viles es distribueixen en dues plantes i compten amb àrea de terrassa en planta inferior i planta superior, plaça de garatge exterior i possible instal·lació de pèrgola, aprofitant al màxim l'entorn i el clima de l'illa. S'ofereix, a més, una opció d'upgrade per als propietaris que vulguin afegir una piscina privada.Situat a Cala Romàntica, a només cinc minuts de la cala Estany d'en Mas, Sunrise Bay Residences és un veritable oasi de pau en una zona exclusiva de Mallorca.Un lloc per gaudir de l'essència mediterrània i establir el seu nou hogar.Vine a visitar-lo i descobreix-lo en primera persona.VISITA EL NOSTRE WEB: rbconforthouse. com per conèixer tots els habitatges dels quals disposem tant en lloguer com en venda actualment. SEGUEIX-NOS A XARXES:FACEBOOK RBconforthouse.INSTAGRAM RBconforthouse.~]]></descrip12>
    <titulo15><![CDATA[]]></titulo15>
    <descrip15><![CDATA[VISITE AL PIANO PILOTA DISPONIBILI.Presentiamo Sunrise Bay Residences, un complesso residenziale esclusivo sulla costa orientale di Maiorca, un'enclave unica e naturale sull'isola più paradisiaca del Mediterraneo.Goditi le sue piscine all'aperto in diverse aree del complesso, palestra dotata di attrezzature sportive, sala cinema, gastrobar, business center, zona relax attrezzata con sauna, getti d'acqua e idromassaggio.In Sunrise Bay Residences troverai ville di 2, 3 e 4 camere da letto di diverse tipologie fino a 150 m² per scegliere quella che meglio si adatta al tuo stile di vita e goderti il massimo benessere all'aria aperta. Informati senza impegno e ti forniremo tutte le informazioni di cui hai bisogno.Ogni villa è stata progettata con cura per integrarsi perfettamente con l'ambiente mediterraneo della zona. La distribuzione strategica consente la connessione interna ed esterna nella maggior parte dei soggiorni per ricevere la massima entrata di luce naturale, con conseguenti soggiorni ampi, luminosi e accoglienti.Le sue ampie vetrate uniscono terrazze e saloni per massimizzare lo spazio e far arrivare la luce di Maiorca in ogni angolo, grazie anche a una distribuzione aperta e fluida.Sono dotate di tutto il necessario per una vita comoda.Carpenteria esterna in PVC o alluminio laccato con rottura di ponte termico e doppio vetro con camera d'aria, per una maggiore efficienza energetica garantendo il comfort termico nell'abitazione, porta di accesso all'abitazione di sicurezza, porte interne di passaggio laccate in bianco, armadi a muro, laminato pavimento galleggiante di finitura sintetica, bagni attrezzati con sanitari, piatto doccia e rubinetterie con pavimento in gres porcellanato, cucine con mobili alti e bassi con possibilità di rimessaggio, piano di lavoro in tinta con le ante dell'arredo, elettrodomestici.La sua installazione di freddo/caldo conferisce un ulteriore benessere e comfort.Tutte le ville sono distribuite su due piani e dispongono di area terrazzo al piano inferiore e al piano superiore, posto auto esterno e possibile installazione di pergolato, sfruttando al massimo l'ambiente e il clima dell'isola. Viene inoltre offerta un'opzione di upgrade per i proprietari che desiderano aggiungere una piscina privata.Situato a Cala Romantica, a soli cinque minuti dalla cala Estany d'en Mas, Sunrise Bay Residences è una vera oasi di pace in una zona esclusiva di Maiorca.Un luogo per godere dell'essenza mediterranea e stabilire la tua nuova casa.Vieni a visitarlo e scoprilo in prima persona.VISITA IL NOSTRO SITO WEB: rbconforthouse. com per conoscere tutte le abitazioni di cui disponiamo sia in affitto che in vendita attualmente. SEGUICI SUI SOCIAL:FACEBOOK RBconforthouse.INSTAGRAM RBconforthouse.~]]></descrip15>
    <titulo16><![CDATA[]]></titulo16>
    <descrip16><![CDATA[]]></descrip16>
    <titulo17><![CDATA[]]></titulo17>
    <descrip17><![CDATA[WIZYTY NA PIĘTRO PILOTÓW DOSTĘPNE.Przedstawiamy Sunrise Bay Residences, ekskluzywny kompleks mieszkaniowy na wschodnim wybrzeżu Majorki, wyjątkowej i naturalnej enklawie na najbardziej rajskiej wyspie Morza Śródziemnego.Ciesz się basenami zewnętrznymi na różnych działkach kompleksu, siłownią wyposażoną w sprzęt sportowy, salą kinową, barem gastronomicznym, centrum biznesowym, strefą relaksu wyposażoną w saunę, hydromasaż i jacuzzi.W Sunrise Bay Residences znajdziesz wille z 2, 3 i 4 sypialniami o różnej typologii do 150 m², abyś mógł wybrać tę, która najlepiej odpowiada Twojemu stylowi życia i cieszyć się maksymalnym dobrostanem na świeżym powietrzu. Poinformuj się bez zobowiązań, a my dostarczymy Ci wszystkich potrzebnych informacji.Każda willa została starannie zaprojektowana, aby idealnie wkomponować się w śródziemnomorski klimat okolicy. Strategiczny układ pozwala na połączenie wnętrza i zewnętrza w większości pomieszczeń, aby uzyskać maksymalny dostęp światła naturalnego, co skutkuje przestronnymi, jasnymi i przytulnymi pomieszczeniami.Jego duże okna łączą tarasy i salony, aby zmaksymalizować przestrzeń i sprawić, aby światło Majorki docierało do każdego zakątka, również dzięki otwartemu i płynnemu rozmieszczeniu.Są wyposażone we wszystko, co niezbędne do wygodnego życia.Stolarka zewnętrzna z PVC lub aluminium lakierowanego z przegrodą termiczną i podwójnymi szybami z komorą powietrzną, dla większej efektywności energetycznej gwarantującej komfort termiczny w domu, drzwi wejściowe do domu antywłamaniowe, wewnętrzne drzwi przejściowe lakierowane na biało, szafy wnękowe, podłoga laminowana z wykończeniem syntetycznym, łazienki wyposażone w sanitariaty, brodzik prysznicowy i armaturę z podłogą z porcelany, kuchnie z meblami górnymi i dolnymi z możliwościami przechowywania, blat w odcieniu pasującym do drzwi mebli, sprzęt AGD.Jego instalacja chłodnicza / grzewcza zapewnia dodatkowe samopoczucie i wygodę.Wszystkie wille rozmieszczone są na dwóch piętrach i posiadają taras na parterze i piętrze, zewnętrzne miejsce parkingowe i możliwość montażu pergoli, maksymalnie wykorzystując otoczenie i klimat wyspy. Ponadto właścicielom, którzy chcą dobudować prywatny basen, oferowana jest opcja modernizacji.Sunrise Bay Residences, położony w Cala Romantica, zaledwie pięć minut od zatoki Estany d'en Mas, to prawdziwa oaza spokoju w ekskluzywnej części Majorki.Miejsce, w którym można cieszyć się śródziemnomorską esencją i założyć nowy dom.Przyjdź i odkryj to osobiście.ODWIEDŹ NASZĄ STRONĘ INTERNETOWĄ: rbconforthouse. com, aby poznać wszystkie domy, którymi dysponujemy zarówno na wynajem, jak i na sprzedaż.ŚLEDŹ NAS W SIECIACH:FACEBOOK RBconforthouse.INSTAGRAM RBconforthouse.~]]></descrip17>
    <titulo18><![CDATA[]]></titulo18>
    <descrip18><![CDATA[]]></descrip18>
    <titulo19><![CDATA[]]></titulo19>
    <descrip19><![CDATA[BESØG TIL VISNINGSLEJLIGHED TILGÆNGELIG.Vi præsenterer Sunrise Bay Residences, et eksklusivt boligkompleks på Mallorcas østkyst, en unik og naturlig enklave på Middelhavets mest paradisiske ø.Nyd dets udendørs swimmingpools på forskellige grunde i komplekset, fitnesscenter udstyret med sportsudstyr, biograf, gastrobar, business center, afslapningsområde udstyret med sauna, vandstråler og hydromassage.I Sunrise Bay Residences finder du villaer med 2, 3 og 4 soveværelser af forskellige typer på op til 150 m², så du kan vælge den, der passer bedst til din livsstil og nyde maksimal velvære udendørs. Få oplysninger uden forpligtelse, og vi vil give dig alle de oplysninger, du har brug for.Hver villa er omhyggeligt designet, så den integreres perfekt med områdets middelhavsatmosfære. Den strategiske fordeling muliggør indvendig og udvendig forbindelse i de fleste opholdsrum for at modtage maksimalt naturligt lysindfald, hvilket resulterer i rummelige, lyse og hyggelige opholdsrum.De store vinduer forbinder terrasser og opholdsstuer for at maksimere pladsen og få Mallorcas lys til at nå hvert hjørne, takket være en åben og flydende fordeling.De er udstyret med alt, hvad der er nødvendigt for et behageligt liv.Udvendigt snedkeri i PVC eller lakeret aluminium med brudt termisk bro og dobbeltglas med luftrum for større energieffektivitet, der garanterer termisk komfort i boligen, sikkerhedsadgangsdør til boligen, indvendige døre lakeret i hvidt, indbyggede skabe, lamineret flydende gulv med syntetisk finish, badeværelser udstyret med sanitet, brusebakke og armaturer med porcelænsgulv, køkkener med overskabe og underskabe med opbevaringsmuligheder, bordplade i tone, der matcher møblernes døre, hårde hvidevarer.Dens installation af kulde / varme giver et ekstra velvære og komfort.Alle villaer er fordelt på to etager og har terrasseområde i underetagen og øverste etage, udvendig garageplads og mulighed for installation af pergola, der udnytter øens omgivelser og klima maksimalt. Der tilbydes desuden en opgraderingsmulighed for ejere, der ønsker at tilføje en privat pool.Beliggende i Cala Romantica, kun fem minutter fra bugten Estany d'en Mas, er Sunrise Bay Residences en sand oase af fred i et eksklusivt område på Mallorca.Et sted at nyde Middelhavets essens og etablere dit nye hjem.Kom og besøg det og oplev det personligt.BESØG VORES HJEMMESIDE: rbconforthouse. com for at se alle de boliger, vi har til rådighed, både til leje og salg i øjeblikket. FØLG OS PÅ SOCIALE MEDIER:FACEBOOK RBconforthouse.INSTAGRAM RBconforthouse.~]]></descrip19>
    <titulo22><![CDATA[]]></titulo22>
    <descrip22><![CDATA[]]></descrip22>
    <titulo23><![CDATA[]]></titulo23>
    <descrip23><![CDATA[]]></descrip23>
    <titulo25><![CDATA[]]></titulo25>
    <descrip25><![CDATA[]]></descrip25>
    <estadoficha>1</estadoficha>
    <exclu>0</exclu>
    <tour>https://crm.inmovilla.com/fotosvr/tour.php?cod=22447562.11855</tour>
    <keyagente>180707</keyagente>
    <agente><![CDATA[Rafael Barba Barona]]></agente>
    <email_agente>rafael@rbconforthouse.com</email_agente>
    <prefijo_tlf_agente>34</prefijo_tlf_agente>
    <tlf_agente>696649243</tlf_agente>
    <numpanos>0</numpanos>
    <numfotos>30</numfotos>
    <foto1 eti="fachada">https://fotos15.apinmo.com/11855/22447562/3-1.jpg</foto1>
    <foto2 eti="fachada">https://fotos15.apinmo.com/11855/22447562/3-2.jpg</foto2>
    <foto3 eti="fachada">https://fotos15.apinmo.com/11855/22447562/3-3.jpg</foto3>
    <foto4 eti="piscina">https://fotos15.apinmo.com/11855/22447562/3-4.jpg</foto4>
    <foto5 eti="terraza">https://fotos15.apinmo.com/11855/22447562/3-5.jpg</foto5>
